Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1888-1984; Series III
  - Short stories
    - "A preface to life", 1928 (Box 163, Folder 519)
    - "Rescuers of the Perishing", undated (Box 163, Folder 520)
  - Speeches
    - Correspondence, A, 1940 (Box 163, Folder 521 - 523)
    - Correspondence, B-E, 1940 (Box 164, Folder 524 - 539)
    - Correspondence, F-K, 1940 (Box 165, Folder 540 - 553)
    - Correspondence, L-R, 1940 (Box 166, Folder 554 - 571)
    - Correspondence, S-Z, 1940 (Box 167, Folder 572 - 590)
    - Invitations to speak, 1940-1941 (Box 168, Folder 591 - 593)
    - Speeches, articles, and notes
      - [ca 1932] (Box 168, Folder 594)
      - 1934 (Box 168, Folder 595)
      - 1936 (Box 168, Folder 596 - 601)
      - 1937 (Box 168, Folder 602 - 605)
      - 1937-1943 (Box 168, Folder 606 - 607)
      - 1938 (Box 168, Folder 608 - 611)
      - 1939 (Box 169, Folder 612 - 617)
      - 1940 (Box 169, Folder 618 - 620)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 169, Folder 621)
      - 1940-1943 (Box 169, Folder 622 - 625)
      - 1940-1946 (Box 169, Folder 626 - 629)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 170, Folder 630 - 634)
      - 1943 (Box 170, Folder 635 - 637)
      - 1947 (Box 170, Folder 638 - 642)
      - 1948 (Box 170, Folder 643 - 644)
      - 1949 [includes photographs] (Box 170, Folder 645 - 649)
      - 1949-1952 (Box 171, Folder 650 - 651)
      - 1950 (Box 171, Folder 652 - 657)
      - 1952 (Box 171, Folder 658 - 662)
      - 1953 (Box 171, Folder 663 - 669)
        See also: Oversize Folder 73
      - 1954, [1952-1954] (Box 172, Folder 670 - 677)
        See also: Oversize Folder 14
      - 1960 "Campaign speech for Sen. Bridges and V.P. Nixon" (Box 172, Folder 678 - 680)
      - n.d. (Box 172, Folder 681 - 685)
  - Writings by others
    - Aaronsohn, Aaron, 1915-1919 (Box 173, Folder 1-11)
    - Aaronsohn, Aaron, 1915-1919 (Box 174, Folder 1-7)
    - Aaronsohn, Aaron, 1915-1919 (Box 175, Folder 1-6)
    - Angel, William David, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 686 - 690)
    - Beck, Józef, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 691 - 696)
    - Bullitt, Aimée Ernesta Drinker, 1921, undated (Box 176, Folder 697)
    - Chen Pin-ho, 1933 (Box 176, Folder 698)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 699 - 704)
    - De Cary, Madame Marteau de Langle, 1947 (Box 177, Folder 705 - 706)
    - De La Raudière, M. Pierre, undated (Box 177, Folder 707 - 713)
    - Kennan, George F., 1946-1947 (Box 177, Folder 714)
    - Langer, William [includes correspondence], 1944-1945 (Box 177, Folder 715 - 723)
    - Reynaud, Paul, 1941 (Box 178, Folder 724 - 736)
    - Schur, Max, undated (Box 178, Folder 737)
    - Streit, Charles K., 1943 (Box 178, Folder 738)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936, 1941-1942, 1950-1951, undated (Box 178, Folder 739 - 746)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 179, Folder 747 - 751)
  - Unidentified manuscripts, 1916, 1933-1959, undated (Box 179, Folder 752 - 764)
    See also: Oversize Folder 75
- Photographs, 1891-1964; Series IV
  This series consists of photographic prints, negatives, and photo albums. The vast majority of the photographs are black and white and most are in fair condition. The series is organized into two sections: Diplomatic-public service and Personal. Within the Diplomatic and public service section, the materials are arranged by position held by Bullitt and by subject. Within the personal section, the materials are organized by subject. The few negatives in the series are filed along with the photographic prints and albums. The photographs document William Bullitt's career as a diplomat, his social and family life, and his work as a journalist in the 1940s and 1950s reporting on world affairs, especially in Asia.
  The bulk of the photographs concerning Bullitt's diplomatic and public service relate to his ambassadorships to the Soviet Union from 1933 to 1936 and to France from 1936 to 1940. Most of the Soviet Union images picture Bullitt with unidentified groups or individuals; some of these appear to involve government business or Soviet officials but with many it is unclear. Only a small portion of these photographs are specifically identified. These include captioned press photographs of Ambassador Bullitt's arrival in the USSR in December 1933 and his welcome by Michael Kalinin and other Soviet officials as well as Ambassador Bullitt playing polo with Soviet soldiers. A much greater proportion of the photographs from Bullitt's service in France are identified. Many of these are captioned press photographs of Bullitt meeting with French officials, participating in ceremonies, and generally performing his duties as ambassador. Other identified photographs include the June 1940 bombardment of Paris, Bullitt's 1938 visit to Lorraine, and the 1937 visit to France of Sara Roosevelt, Franklin D. Roosevelt's mother. Besides the material related to his ambassadorships, there are small numbers of photographs concerning Bullitt's particiation in the Paris Peace Conference of 1919, his candidacy for the mayor of Philadelphia, and his service as an Ambassador-at-large, a Special Assistant to the Secretary of the Navy, and a military aide in the Free French Armed Forces.
  This series also contains a large selection of photographs related to Bullitt's social and family life. A variety of photographs depict him throughout his life from infancy into retirement. Family pictures include those of his extended family, his first wife Aimée Ernesta Drinker Bullitt, his second wife Louise Bryant, his daughter Anne, and Refik Ishmail, a Turkish boy who lived with the Bullitt family. Other photographs picture friends and professional acquaintances including Bullitt's long-time friend and aide Carmel Offie. A large number of photographs relate to Camp Pasquaney, a New Hampshire summer camp Bullitt attended as a boy. Among the personal photographs are included images from Bullitt's travels to East Asia in the late 1940s and 1950s as a journalist. These photographs capture his visits to South Korea, Japan, Indochina, and the Philippines and some of the unidentified photographs may picture other countries like Taiwan where Bullitt spent a good deal of time. A large portion of the images from the Far East depict Bullitt meeting with American and Asian military personnel.
  - Diplomatic and public service
    - Paris Peace Conference, 1919 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Ambassador to the USSR
      - General, 1934-1936, undated (Box 180, Folder 2 - 6)
        See also: Oversize Folder 66
      - Animal husbandry, undated (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Arrival, 1933 December (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Chiang Kai-shek, [1934?] (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Embassy airplane, undated (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Polo, undated (Box 180, Folder 11 - 12)
      - Warsaw, [1935?] (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Ambassador to France
      - General, 1936-1940 (Box 180, Folder 14 - 20)
        See also: Oversize Folder 60
      - General, undated (Box 181, Folder 21 - 23)
      - Bombardment of Paris, 1940 June 3 (Box 181, Folder 24)
      - Confrérie du Tastevin, 1937 (Box 181, Folder 25)
      - Herrick monument, 1937 (Box 181, Folder 26)
      - Joan of Arc monument, 1943 (Box 181, Folder 27)
      - Lorraine visit [album], 1938 (Box 181, Folder 28)
      - Memorial Day, 1940 (Box 181, Folder 29)
      - Photograph lists, undated (Box 181, Folder 30)
      - Radio Fécamp [album], undated (Box 181, Folder 31)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1938 (Box 181, Folder 32)
      - Roosevelt, Sara Delano, visit of, 1937 (Box 181, Folder 33)
      - Stalin, Joseph and Joachim Von Ribbentrop, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 34)
    - Ambassador-at-Large [Cairo], 1941 (Box 181, Folder 35)
    - Assistant to the Secretary of the Navy
      - General, 1943 (Box 181, Folder 36)
      - London, 1942 September (Box 181, Folder 37)
    - Philadelphia mayoral campaign, 1943 (Box 181, Folder 38)
      See also: Oversize Folder 65
    - Free French Armed Forces, undated (Box 181, Folder 39)
    - Legion of Merit, 1947 (Box 181, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 181, Folder 41)
  - Personal
    - People
      - Bullitt, William C.
        - Adult, 1920, 1938-1943, 1956, undated (Box 182, Folder 42 - 45)
          See also: Oversize Folder 62 - 64
        - Youth, [1891], undated (Box 182, Folder 46 - 49)
        - Bullitt, William C., Louise Bryant, and Anne Bullitt [includes negatives], 1928, undated (Box 182, Folder 50)
        - Bullitt, William C. with Anne Bullitt, 1936, undated (Box 183, Folder 51 - 52)
        - Bullitt, William C. with Arthur W. Radford, 1956 (Box 183, Folder 53)
        - Bullitt, William C. with Carmel Offie, circa 1936 (Box 183, Folder 54 - 55)
        - Bullitt, William C. with Chiang Kai-shek, [1941]
          See: Oversize Folder 62 - 64
        - Bullitt, William C. with others [includes negatives], [ca 1920-1921], 1932-1938, 1944, 1952-1957, undated (Box 183, Folder 56 - 62)
        - Bullitt family with Refik Ishmail, undated (Box 183, Folder 63)
      - Blum, Leon, 1946 (Box 183, Folder 64)
      - Bryant, Louise, undated (Box 183, Folder 65)
      - Bullitt, Aimée Ernesta Drinker, undated (Box 183, Folder 66)
      - Bullitt, Anne [includes negatives], 1937, undated (Box 183, Folder 67)
      - Bullitt family, undated (Box 183, Folder 68 - 69)
      - Camp Pasquaney, New Hampshire, undated (Box 184, Folder 70 - 73)
      - Offie, Carmel, [ca 1936], undated (Box 184, Folder 74)
      - Rhee, Syngman, 1956 (Box 184, Folder 75)
      - Schelda and Henri, undated (Box 184, Folder 76)
      - Other individuals, 1912, 1917, 1933-1940, 1950, 1955, 1963-1964, undated (Box 184, Folder 77 - 81)
      - Small groups, [ca 1932-1933?], 1950-1963, undated (Box 184, Folder 82)
    - Far East
      - General, [ca 1955-1956] (Box 184, Folder 83 - 84)
      - Indochina, 1947 (Box 184, Folder 85)
      - Institut du Cancer L'Indochine (Hanoi), 1949 (Box 184, Folder 86)
      - Seoul, 1956 (Box 184, Folder 87)
      - Tokyo, [ca 1956] (Box 184, Folder 88)
        See also: Oversize Folder 67
      - Tokyo Army Hospital, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 89)
      - Travel, 1952-1953, undated (Box 185, Folder 90 - 91)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Animals, undated (Box 185, Folder 92 - 93)
      - Artwork, undated (Box 185, Folder 94)
      - Ashfield farm, undated (Box 185, Folder 95)
      - Buildings and objects, 1956, 1962, undated (Box 185, Folder 96)
        See also: Oversize Folder 61
      - Capri, [ca 1935] (Box 185, Folder 97)
      - Chinese communist money, 1933, undated (Box 185, Folder 98)
      - Haiti, undated (Box 185, Folder 99)
      - Turkey, [ca 1932-1937] (Box 185, Folder 100)
- Motion Pictures and Sound Recordings, 1933-1952; Series V
  This series contains motion picture film and a sound recording that document Bullitt's diplomatic career and personal life. The five 35mm films appear to date from the 1930s when Bullitt was ambassador to the Soviet Union and then France and relate to various aspects of his time in those positions. The sound recording is of a 1952 address broadcast from a Yankton, South Dakota radio station in which Bullitt expresses his support for the candidacy of Robert Taft to be the Republican Party nominee for president.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - Motion pictures
    - "L'Ambassadeur Chez Les Vignerons", undated
      - Duplicate negative of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 186)
      - Answer print of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 186M)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 186-D)
      - VHS use copy (Box 186U1)
      - DVD use copy (Box 186U2)
    - "Ambassador Wm. C. Bullitt and daughter sailing, Ambassador Wm. C. Bullitt in Russia, Russian Envoy in New York", undated
      - Duplicate negative of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 187)
      - Answer print of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 187M)
      - Duplicating master [restricted; may not be played] (Box 187-D)
      - VHS use copy (Box 187U1)
      - DVD use copy (Box 187U2)
    - "American Ambassador" [France], undated
      - Duplicate negative of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 188)
      - Answer print of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 188M)
      - Duplicating master [restricted; may not be played] (Box 188-D)
      - VHS use copy (Box 188U1)
      - DVD use copy (Box 188U2)
    - "French Minister of Agriculture and American Ambassador at horse show," Twenty Century Fox, undated
      - Duplicate negative of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 189)
      - Answer print of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 189M)
      - Duplicating master [restricted; may not be played] (Box 189-D)
      - VHS use copy (Box 189U1)
      - DVD use copy (Box 189U2)
    - "Why Russian recognition matters to the United States", [ca 1933]
      - Duplicate negative of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 190)
      - Answer print of original film [restricted; may not be played] (Box 190M)
      - Duplicating master [restricted; may not be played] (Box 190-D)
      - VHS use copy (Box 190U1)
      - DVD use copy (Box 190U2)
  - Sound recording, Bullitt radio speech supporting Robert Taft, WNAX Yankton, South Dakota, 1952
    - Original [transferred to Historical Sound Recordings]
    - Duplicating master [restricted; may not be played] (Box 191-D)
    - Use copy (Box 191U)
- Personal and Family Papers, 1840-1998; Series VI
  This series is divided into Personal papers and Family papers. The personal papers are comprised of Bullitt's legal, financial, and medical documents, subject files, appointment books, school papers, address books, membership cards, drawings, objects, and other materials of a personal nature. The legal documents include wills, passports, and deeds and the financial material includes Bullitt's personal financial records, such as bank statements, bills, receipts, and checkbooks, from his service as ambassador to the Soviet Union and France. The large assortment of appointment books document Bullitt's daily activities from the start of his ambassadorship in France to the end of his life with occasional gaps.
  The subject files reflect Bullitt's personal, political, and journalistic interests. The larger subject files concern his involvement with Georgetown University, his support for a unified Europe, and ties to Taiwan including a file on Chang Ming-kai, a servant employed by Bullitt whose treatment by General Chang Quo-chang became the subject of controversy between Bullitt and Chiang Kai-shek. Three folders of material address Bullitt's involvement in the resignation of Sumner Welles and contain evidence Bullitt gathered that Welles had made criminal homosexual advances on railroad porters. Because the Welles folders contain notes written in the hand of Anne Bullitt and other material apparently added by her after her father's death, it is not clear if these files were originally assembled by William Bullitt or by Anne gathering together materials largely from her father's papers. There is also a small amount of material in the subject files concerning Louise Bryant and Bullitt's divorce from her.
  The family papers are made up of correspondence, writings by Bullitt's parents, and materials collected by Anne Bullitt. The correspondence consists of letters between Bullitt relatives that are neither to nor from William C. Bullitt, Jr, and much of it predates Bullitt's birth. Included in the material collected by Anne are correspondence, family history research, photographs, legal documents, and printed matter. Most of the material concerns her parents William C. Bullitt, Jr. and Louise Bryant. This includes correspondence with researchers interested in her parents and other correspondence specifically concerning the biography published about her father So Close to Greatness and the revisions she demanded under the threat of a lawsuit. The last folder of "Researchers" correspondence contains a detailed bibliography concerning Bullitt. There is also correspondence with her uncle Orville H. Bullitt about the book, For the President, Personal and Secret, he edited, which contained Bullitt's correspondence with President Franklin Roosevelt. Anne's materials also include correspondence with her fourth husband Senator Daniel Brewster and a large selection of his publicity photographs.
  - Personal
    - Address books (Box 192, Folder 1 - 6)
    - Appointment books, 1928, 1936-1937 (Box 192, Folder 7 - 9)
    - Appointment books, 1937-1940 (Box 193, Folder 10 - 13)
    - Appointment books, 1942-1943 (Box 194, Folder 14 - 18)
    - Appointment books, 1944-1950 (Box 195, Folder 19 - 26)
    - Appointment books, 1951-1960 (Box 196, Folder 27 - 36)
    - Appointment books, 1961-1966, undated (Box 197, Folder 37 - 42)
    - Business cards and addresses (Box 197, Folder 43 - 44)
    - Christmas card lists, 1937-1943 (Box 197, Folder 45)
    - Christmas cards, 1939 (Box 197, Folder 46 - 47)
    - Christmas cards, 1939 (Box 198, Folder 48 - 54)
    - Drawings, undated (Box 198, Folder 55 - 57)
    - Financial
      - General
        - Accounts, 1913-1931 (Box 199, Folder 58 - 65)
        - Accounts, 1913-1931 (Box 200, Folder 66 - 67)
        - Income tax returns, 1937-1942, 1947-1955 (Box 200, Folder 68 - 69)
        - Securities certificates, 1923-1925 (Box 200, Folder 70)
      - Ambassador to the USSR
        - Checkbooks, 1934-1937 (Box 200, Folder 71)
        - Girard Trust, 1933-1936 (Box 200, Folder 72 - 74)
        - Morgan et Cie., 1934-1936
          See: Oversize Folder 50 - 51
        - State Bank of the USSR, 1934-1935 (Box 200, Folder 75)
        - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 200, Folder 76)
      - Ambassador to France (Box 201)
        - Accounts, 1938-1940 (Box 200, Folder 77 - 82)
        - Banking, 1936-1940
          See: Oversize Folder 27 - 31
        - Bills, receipted, 1937 (Box 200, Folder 83)
        - Bills, receipted, 1937-1938 (Box 202, Folder 84 - 88)
        - Bills, receipted, 1938-1939 (Box 203, Folder 89 - 96)
        - Bills, receipted, 1939-1940 (Box 204, Folder 97 - 101)
        - Insurance, 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 102 - 104)
        - Miscellaneous, 1938-1940 (Box 204, Folder 105)
    - Invitations, general (Box 204, Folder 106)
    - Invitations, White House for Anne, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 107)
    - Legal, 1891-1967 (Box 205, Folder 108 - 115)
      See also: Oversize Folder 80
      See also: Oversize Folder 47
    - Medical, 1913-1917, 1946, 1959-1966 (Box 205, Folder 116 - 123)
    - Membership cards and passes (Box 205, Folder 124)
    - Memorabilia (Box 205, Folder 125)
    - Objects
      - Democratic National Convention badge, 1944 (Box 205, Folder 126)
      - Wallet with Franklin Delano Roosevelt monogram, undated (Box 205, Folder 127)
    - Paintings, undated (Box 205, Folder 128)
    - School
      - De Lancey School English journals, undated (Box 206, Folder 129 - 132)
      - Diary, 1911 (Box 206, Folder 133)
      - Essays, 1910, undated (Box 206, Folder 134 - 137)
      - Exams, undated (Box 207, Folder 138)
      - Language exercises, undated (Box 207, Folder 139)
      - Law notes [Harvard Law School], [ca 1914] (Box 207, Folder 140 - 141)
      - Lecture notes, undated (Box 207, Folder 142 - 146)
      - Yale, miscellaneous [includes essays and correspondence], 1909-1914 (Box 207, Folder 147 - 149)
    - Subject files
      - Alba [includes photographs], 1949-1950 (Box 207, Folder 150)
      - Anti Kommunistischer Volksbund für Frieden und Freiheit, 1954 (Box 207, Folder 151)
      - Automobile, 1947-1950 (Box 207, Folder 152)
      - Bryant, Louise, 1928, 1936 (Box 207, Folder 153)
      - Bryant divorce, 1929, undated (Box 207, Folder 154 - 156)
      - Bullitt, Anne
        - Birth, 1924 (Box 208, Folder 157)
        - College, 1944 (Box 208, Folder 158)
        - Wedding, 1947 (Box 208, Folder 159 - 160)
        - Writings, undated (Box 208, Folder 161 - 162)
      - Camp Pasquaney, 1909 (Box 208, Folder 163)
      - Catholic Labor Party, 1947-1949 (Box 208, Folder 164)
      - Chang Ming-kai, 1955-1956 (Box 208, Folder 165 - 167)
      - China treaty, 1946 (Box 208, Folder 168)
      - Dogs, 1920, 1939-1944 (Box 208, Folder 169 - 172)
      - Europe mission, 1932 (Box 208, Folder 173)
      - Europe trip [includes journal], 1914 (Box 208, Folder 174)
      - European Parliament, Second Congress, 1948 (Box 208, Folder 175 - 179)
      - European Parliament, Second Congress, 1948 (Box 209, Folder 180 - 181)
        See also: Oversize Folder 37
      - French Institute, 1946 (Box 209, Folder 182)
      - Georgetown University, 1950-1957 (Box 209, Folder 183 - 191)
        See also: Oversize Folder 3
      - German paintings, 1948 (Box 209, Folder 192)
      - Horse pedigrees, undated (Box 209, Folder 193)
      - Internal revenue code, amendment to section 1221, 1962 (Box 209, Folder 194)
      - Kaoshiung House, 1952-1953 (Box 209, Folder 195)
        See also: Oversize Folder 95
      - Lattimore, Owen, 1936-1954, undated (Box 210, Folder 196 - 197)
      - Liquor, 1943-1944, undated (Box 210, Folder 198)
      - Offie, Carmel, 1949 (Box 210, Folder 199)
      - Pai Shiu Chuan, 1953-1954 (Box 210, Folder 200)
      - Paris apartment, 1953 (Box 210, Folder 201)
      - Poland, 1941-1942, undated (Box 210, Folder 202)
      - Religion in Russia, 1941-1943 (Box 210, Folder 203)
      - Republican Kansas state platform, 1948 (Box 210, Folder 204)
      - Republican presidential primaries, 1952 (Box 210, Folder 205)
      - Saint Joseph's College honorary degree, 1958 (Box 210, Folder 206)
      - Spain, 1949-1950 (Box 210, Folder 207)
      - Stevenson, Adlai, 1952 (Box 210, Folder 208)
      - Stolen jewelry, 1946 (Box 210, Folder 209)
      - Stud book rules, 1937 (Box 210, Folder 210)
      - Travel [includes photographs], 1924-1929, 1948-1956 (Box 210, Folder 211 - 213)
      - United Europe, 1948-1949 (Box 210, Folder 214 - 215)
      - War rationing, 1942 (Box 210, Folder 216)
      - Welles, Sumner, 1941-1943 (Box 210, Folder 217 - 219)
      - Whang Ey-chan, 1958 (Box 210, Folder 220)
      - White, Thomas D., 1961 (Box 210, Folder 221)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 210, Folder 222)
      See also: Oversize Folder 58
  - Family
    - General
      - Correspondence, 1840, 1866-1915, undated (Box 210, Folder 223 - 225)
      - Correspondence, 1840, 1866-1915, undated (Box 211, Folder 226 - 233)
      - Diary of Louisa Horwitz Bullitt, 1910-1914 (Box 211, Folder 234)
      - Letters of sympathy on death of William Christian Bullitt, Sr., 1914 (Box 211, Folder 235)
      - Notebook of William Christian Bullitt, Sr., 1877 (Box 211, Folder 236)
    - Bullitt, Anne Moen
      - Address book, undated (Box 212, Folder 237)
      - Childhood, undated (Box 212, Folder 238)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1929-1995 (Box 212, Folder 239 - 247)
        - Ashfield, Massachusetts, 1992, undated (Box 212, Folder 248)
        - Brewster, Daniel, 1967-1971 (Box 212, Folder 249 - 252)
          See also: Oversize Folder 77
          See also: Series VI. Personal and Family Papers, 1840-1998 Folder 337 - 350
          See also: Series VI. Personal and Family Papers, 1840-1998 Folder 351 - 353
        - Brewster, Daniel, 1967-1971 (Box 213, Folder 253 - 260)
        - Bullitt, Orville H., 1967-1977 (Box 213, Folder 261 - 269)
        - Death of William C. Bullitt, 1967 (Box 213, Folder 270 - 272)